<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ConcussionCheck</string>
    <string name="latitude">52.2084083</string>
    <string name="longitude">0.0856367</string>
    <string name="symptom1">Loss of consciousness or responsiveness</string>
    <string name="symptom2">Change in vision or hearing</string>
    <string name="symptom3">Increasing confusion or irritability</string>
    <string name="symptom4">Nausea or vomiting</string>
    <string name="symptom5">Seizure or convulsion</string>
    <string name="symptom6">Weakness, tingling, or burning in arms or legs</string>
    <string name="symptom7">Headache</string>
    <string name="symptom8">Dizziness or balance problems</string>
    <string name="symptom9">Confusion</string>
    <string name="symptom10">Nausea</string>
    <string name="symptom11">Blank or vacant look</string>
    <string name="symptom12">Neck Pain</string>
    <string name="symptom13">“Don’t feel right”</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nearest_a_e">Map</string>
    <string name="maddockQuestions">
        The player is not showing immediate symptoms of concussion. However, if in doubt, or if symptoms
        arise later, please remove the player from the field and seek medical attention.\n\n
        The following questions can be used as an additional screening tool for adults and children over 13:\n
        &#8226; At what venue are we today?\n
        &#8226; Which half is it now?\n
        &#8226; Who scored last in this match?\n
        &#8226; What did you play last week?\n
        &#8226; Did your team win the last game?\n
    </string>
    <string name="pregamePrimer">
        What should I be watching out for?\n\n
        &#8226; Direct blow to the head or body\n
        &#8226; Whiplash type movements of the head and neck\n
        &#8226; Player is tackled or collides with another player\n
        &#8226; Player hits the ground\n\n
        Skill tips for avoiding concussion injury\n\n
        &#8226; Lower the height of tacklers and the associated body position of tacklers\n
        &#8226; Change the technique or technical execution of higher,
        upright tackles so that head contact is avoided or reduced
    </string>
    <string name="furtherInfo">
        Concussion is the most commonly diagnosed injury in the community game in England, making
        17% of all injuries. There was one diagnosed concussion for a team every 11.4 games in
        England, although the incidence rates may be higher than this.72% of concussions occurs in
        the tackle.40% of all concussions are to the ball carrier in the tackle and 32% to the
        tackler.\n\nConcussion can occur from head contact with the body in a tackle or head contact
        with the ground. Concussions can occur with no direct head contact.Female Players tend to
        report more severe and prolonged symptoms. Children tend to recover more slowly from
        concussive injury.\n\nConcussion must be taken extremely seriously to safeguard the safety
        and long-term health of players. The majority (80-90%) of concussion symptoms resolve in
        around 7-10 days, with symptoms resolving within 1-2 days in around a third of cases,
        although full recovery will normally take longer than this. Loss of consciousness occurs
        in only 10-15% of concussions.\n\nHeadguards, gumshields and other protective equipment do not
        protect against concussions. Concussion can occur in a game or at training. The onset of
        the effects of concussion maybe delayed for up to 24–48 hours.
    </string>
</resources>