<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ConcussionCheck</string>
    <string name="latitude">52.2084083</string>
    <string name="longitude">0.0856367</string>
    <string name="symptom1">Loss of consciousness or responsiveness</string>
    <string name="symptom2">Change in vision or hearing</string>
    <string name="symptom3">Increasing confusion or irritability</string>
    <string name="symptom4">Nausea or vomiting</string>
    <string name="symptom5">Seizure or convulsion</string>
    <string name="symptom6">Weakness, tingling, or burning in arms or legs</string>
    <string name="symptom7">Headache</string>
    <string name="symptom8">Dizziness or balance problems</string>
    <string name="symptom9">Confusion</string>
    <string name="symptom10">Nausea</string>
    <string name="symptom11">Blank or vacant look</string>
    <string name="symptom12">Neck Pain</string>
    <string name="symptom13">“Don’t feel right”</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nearest_a_e">Map</string>
    <string name="maddockQuestions">
        The player is not showing immediate symptoms of concussion. However, if in doubt, or if symptoms
        arise later, please remove the player from the field and seek medical attention.\n\n
        The following questions can be used as an additional screening tool for adults and children over 13:\n
        &#8226; At what venue are we today?\n
        &#8226; Which half is it now?\n
        &#8226; Who scored last in this match?\n
        &#8226; What did you play last week?\n
        &#8226; Did your team win the last game?\n
    </string>
    <string name="pregamePrimer">
        Concussion is a traumatic brain injury typically resulting from a blow to the head or body
        resulting in forces being transmitted to the brain. The term concussion is vague, each
        concussion is different and can feature very different symptoms. The symptoms can present
        immediately and be short-lived or the onset of symptoms may be delayed and start to occur
        sometime after the initial injury. \n\n
        Some symptoms that require immediate medical attention include: \n
        &#8226; Deteriorating conscious state \n
        &#8226; Severe or increasing headache \n
        &#8226; Unusual behaviour change \n
        &#8226; Increasing confusion or irritability \n
        &#8226; Repeated vomitingWhen responding to a concussion \n\n
        Do: \n
        &#8226; Remove the player immediately. \n
        &#8226; Get an assessment by a health care professional within 24 hours of the incident to ensure
        that there are no significant underlying medical issues. \n
        &#8226; Rest and sleep. \n\n
        Do not: \n
        &#8226; Be left alone in the first 24 hours. \n
        &#8226; Consume alcohol in the 24 hours and/or until symptom free. \n
        &#8226; Drive a motor vehicle in the first hours and/or until symptom free. \n\n
        Players suspected of having concussion or diagnosed with concussion should go through a
        Graduated Return to Play programme &#40;GRTP&#41;.</string>
    <string name="furtherInfo">
        Concussion is the most commonly diagnosed injury in the community game in England, making
        17% of all injuries. There was one diagnosed concussion for a team every 11.4 games in
        England, although the incidence rates may be higher than this.72% of concussions occurs in
        the tackle.40% of all concussions are to the ball carrier in the tackle and 32% to the
        tackler.\n\nConcussion can occur from head contact with the body in a tackle or head contact
        with the ground. Concussions can occur with no direct head contact.Female Players tend to
        report more severe and prolonged symptoms. Children tend to recover more slowly from
        concussive injury.\n\nConcussion must be taken extremely seriously to safeguard the safety
        and long-term health of players. The majority (80-90%) of concussion symptoms resolve in
        around 7-10 days, with symptoms resolving within 1-2 days in around a third of cases,
        although full recovery will normally take longer than this. Loss of consciousness occurs
        in only 10-15% of concussions.\n\nHeadguards, gumshields and other protective equipment do not
        protect against concussions. Concussion can occur in a game or at training. The onset of
        the effects of concussion maybe delayed for up to 24–48 hours.
    </string>
</resources>